- +55 (14) 99635-4942
- pedronogueiramoraes@hotmail.com
- Bauru, São Paulo, Brasil
- <u>/pedronogueiraneto</u>

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science

Unisagrado 2016 - 2020

EXPERTISE

HTML5

CSS₃

PHP

MySQL

Symfony Framework

Linux (Ubuntu)

DNS Management

Docker

Laravel

Rest API

LANGUAGE

English: B2 (Upper-Intermediate)

Spanish: Beginner

Portuguese: Native

PEDRO NOGUEIRA

Fullstack Developer

ABOUT ME

Fullstack Developer specialized in technical support, with over 4 years of experience in developing and supporting web and mobile systems. With strong analytical and problem-solving skills, I am committed to delivering effective, high-quality solutions for production environments and customer support.

WORK EXPERIENCE

November 2020 - Present Arca Solutions

Technical Support Backend Developer

Provide expert tech support for web and mobile solutions using Symfony Framework. Debug and resolve technical issues. Report bugs to the Product team. Independently address minor bugs. Act as Assistant Manager. Lead and manage developers. Contact customers for migration assistance.

o July 2020 - October 2020 Freelancer

Freelance Web Developer

Offered web development service for clients as a freelancer. Developed sites using WordPress. Prospected and supported clients in using websites and digital platforms, such as Google Search Console

O December 2018 - May 2020 2RS Soluções Web

Junior Web Developer

Started as Intern on December 2018 until October 2019, then was hired as Junior Developer.

Developed and maintained a virtual store product using PHP and MySQL. Updated clients on code customizations or bug fixes. Customized stores and landing pages. Held meetings with customers to define project scope and gather feedback